《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
抱歉  你是哪位
I'm sorry, who are you?
安德里亚·罗哈斯
Andrea Rojas.
我把凯特科卖给安德里亚了
I sold CatCo to Andrea.
我们将迎来著名的威廉·戴
Tomorrow, we'll be joined by the renowned William Day.
《泰晤士报》的那位吗
From The Times of London?
我辞职
I quit.
但我有个使命  霍普
But I have a calling, Hope,
那就是拯救人类
and it's to fix mankind.
我从没想到超女会告诉我她的身份
I never thought Supergirl would tell me who she was,
但既然她说了  我就有了机会
but now that she has, I have an opportunity,
我可以利用超女达成我的目的
and I can use Supergirl to achieve my ends.
你是谁
Who are you?
你认不出我吗  弟弟
You don't recognize me. Brother.
谢谢你  超女
Thank you, Supergirl.
没什么
Yeah.
那个女人不应该边走路边发短信
That woman shouldn't have been texting and walking.
纳欣诺市民正准备前往投票站
...as citizens of National City prepare to head to the ballot box
大选如火如荼
为中期选举投票
for the upcoming midterms.
黑曜石之北隐形眼镜
Obsidian North contact lenses,
戴出真的自我
they let you do you,
随时  随地  随心所欲
whenever, wherever, and whatever you want.
没搞错吧
Seriously?
就好像你还不够完美似的
As if you weren't amazing enough,
你居然还是个大厨
you're also a gourmet chef?
不算是
Hardly.
但是  这个早餐是我成名作品
But, I'm famous for this breakfast in particular.
我们这里有荷包蛋  脆培根
So we have poached eggs, crispy bacon,
鲜奶油
fresh whipped cream,
还有
and...
丹佛斯蓝莓薄饼
Danvers blueberry pancakes.
我知道
I know, right?
吃上一口
One bite of these...
你将醉生梦死
and you will die for them.
我真的会死
I really will.
怎么了
‭What's wrong?
我不怎么喜欢蓝莓
I'm not the biggest fan of blueberries.
实际上  我对它们过敏
In fact, I'm deathly allergic.
是吗
You are?
我四岁的时候  吃了一把
When I was four, I eat a handful of them,
然后我喉咙肿了起来
and my throat closed up,
我的脸估计也变成这些蓝莓的颜色
and my face probably turned the color of those blueberries.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
真对不起
I... I am so sorry.
没事的  我那时四岁
It's okay. I was four.
不  我刚才差点害死你
No, but I nearly just killed you.
好吧  你不是没有害死我吗
Okay, you didn't just kill me,
而且我总会随身带着肾上腺素笔
and I always carry an emergency EpiPen with me.
真的吗
Really?
我都不知道
I didn't know that.
没事的
Hey, it's all good.
还有  培根和鲜奶油
Also, bacon and whipped cream
正巧是我在这星球上最喜欢的
happen to be two of my most favorite foods
两种食物
on the planet.
所以你也不怎么喜欢
So, you don't really like
荷包蛋  对不对
poached eggs either, do you?
不怎么喜欢
Not so much.
但你知道我最爱的是什么吗
But do you know what I like more than anything?
你
You.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要早餐
I need breakfast.
还有咖啡
And coffee.
是的  这是你的行为模版
Yes, this is your pattern,
所以我就此进行了准备
which is why I've prepared accordingly.
早餐卷饼
Breakfast burritos!
内含西班牙腊香肠与咖啡油脂
With chorizo and crema,
正符合你喜好
as you like.
加上你的氮气咖啡与额外的冷萃咖啡
Plus your nitro-coffee with an extra shot of cold brew.
这是史上最棒的早晨
This is the best morning ever.
"史上最棒的早晨"
"Best morning ever"?
但这要包含万亿年
But that would include eons,
在这瞬间的前前后后
both before and after this moment.
我觉得你用错了词...
I really think you're misusing the ter--
信息已接收
Message received.
我不敢相信之前居然没看出来
I can't believe I didn't see it before.
安德里亚买下凯特科是想要为黑曜石之北
Andrea bought CatCo to get free global advertising
进行免费全球宣传
for Obsidian North.
然后今天早上
And then this morning
在广场大屏幕上
on the jumbotron
一则重要的选举新闻
an important story about the election
被一个巨大的
was swallowed up
黑曜石广告吞掉了
by a gigantic Obsidian commercial.
简直...
It's...
说到即将到来的大选
Well, speaking of the upcoming election,
我昨晚听到了些有趣的新闻
I got some interesting news last night.
我接到一个电话
I got a call
是一群人
from a group of people
想要推举我做参议员
who want to back me for senator.
参议员
Senator?
-是啊  -真是太棒了
- Yeah. - That's incredible.
我从没想过要涉足政治
I never imagined going into politics.
你逗我呢吧
Are you kidding me?
你去华盛顿对我们来说是好事
We would all be lucky to have you in Washington.
我还收到了一份邀请
I also have an offer to be
成为史密森尼杂志的媒体主管
the media director at the Smithsonian.
所以你这是离开
So how long has it been
凯特科才多久  有12小时吗  真是...
since you left CatCo, what, 12 hours? That's...
这是宇宙提示我正走在正途上
That's the universe telling me I'm on the right path.
我想宇宙正在告诉我
Well, I think the universe is just telling me
我需要打起精神
that I have to keep my spirits up
为正义而战
and fight the good fight.
你的精神看起来挺好的
Your spirits do seem remarkably high
对于一个特别不喜欢新上司的人来说
for someone who strongly dislikes her new boss.
这要感谢莉娜
Well, that's thanks to Lena.
我想我没意识到
I don't think I realized
欺骗她对我来说是多大的重负
how burdened I was by lying to her.
现在她知道我是超女了
And now that she knows I'm Supergirl,
她也原谅了我
and she's forgiven me,
我感觉如释重负了
I feel 1,000 pounds lighter.
好像我无所不能
Like I can do anything.
来吧
Bring it!
荣恩  我们给你带了拿铁
J'onn, we got you a latte.
我的天
Oh, my God.
荣恩
J'onn?
J'onn!
超 女
第五季 第二集
这应该可以暂时缓解疼痛
Well, this should help take away the pain temporarily.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你觉得对你下手的人
You think that whoever did this to you
也是释放了午夜的人吗
was also the person that released Midnight?
对
Yes.
他说他是我哥
He said he was my brother.
起先我不相信他  现在我知道是真的了
At first, I didn't believe him, but now I know it must be true.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
这是一种火星人特有的痛楚
This is specifically a Martian form of agony.
在早期的火星
In the early days of Mars,
有对兄弟俩  福波斯和得摩斯
there were two brothers: Phobos and Deimos.
他们的对抗和血拼
Their rivalry and bloodshed
导致了绿白火星人的分裂
was the reason for the split of the Green and White Martians.
为了防止这种事再次发生
To prevent this ever happening again,
绿火星人被下了诅咒
a curse was placed on the Green Martians.
我们称之为"反目咒"
We called it Fa'ra'too'rik.
是一种兄弟之间互相攻击的惩罚
It is the punishment for brother attacking brother.
但你从没提到过有兄弟
But you've never even mentioned having a brother.
我之前不知道
I never knew of one.
感觉无法想象
Seems unthinkable.
但或许他的存在
But perhaps his existence
被我的父母所隐瞒了
was hidden from me by my parents.
还瞒过了整个火星人的群体心灵力量吗
And hidden by the entire Martian community by their hive mind?
我们会找到他的
We're going to find him,
但我们先要帮你止痛
but first we need to deal with your pain.
地球上没有治愈这种疼痛的办法
There is no cure for this on this planet.
未来有
There is in the future.
我们用Q波
We treat afflicted Euphorians,
为尤弗利星人止痛  他们的脑部结构
an alien race with similar brain structure to Martians,
跟火星人相似
with Q-waves.
那是一种存在于
They are narrow waveforms
X射线和伽马射线之间的狭窄波形
that exist between X and gamma rays.
你们之所以没听说过
You haven't heard of them
是因为直到黑暗时代后期
because Q-waves don't get discovered
Q波才被发现
until sometime in the late dark ages.
其实  凯莉在黑曜石
Actually, Kelly's been using Q-waves
一直把Q波应用于她的脑机接口
as part of her brain computer interface at Obsidian.
现在正是创造未来的好时候
Well, no time like the present to create the future.
尼娅
Nia?
卡拉
Kara,
你得马上赶过来
you need to get here immediately.
罗哈斯女士发飙了
Ms. Rojas is on a rampage,
她要等到所有人都到齐后才肯开始编辑会议
and she won't start the editorial meeting until everyone's present.
我这就过去
I'm on my way.
-你们把荣恩送到凯莉那里去  -好
- You guys get J'onn to Kelly. - Okay.
我会尽快
And I'll have the DEO
让超查部开始对绿火星人进行宽波段扫描
start a broadband scan for Green Martians ASAP.
荣恩
J'onn,
我们会找到你哥哥
we're going to find your brother.
谁伤害了你
Who hurt you?
我去见我弟弟了
I went to see my brother.
他袭击了我
He struck at me
导致我们俩都中了反目咒
and inflicted us both with the sting of Fa'ra'too'rik.
我没法治愈你的疼痛
I cannot cure your affliction,
但我会尽我所能
but I will do what I can
减轻你的痛苦  老朋友
to ease your suffering, old friend.
等我恢复之后
Once I am able,
我会为了我们俩  把荣恩·荣兹的新家庭
I will tear this new family of J'onn J'onzz's apart,
搞得支离破碎
for both of us.
霍普
Hope?
早上好  卢瑟女士
Good morning, Ms. Luthor.
已经到早上了吗
Is it morning?
我忘记了时间
I lost track of time.
我昨晚突然想到一件事
I had an epiphany last night.
黑曜石科技的隐形眼镜
There's something in these lenses
有一种特性
of the Obsidian technology
让我可以改变人类的历程
that's going to allow me to change the course of humanity.
这的确值得高兴
That is an exciting agenda.
你的科学假设是什么
What is your scientific hypothesis?
霍普  你能伤害别人吗
Hope, could you hurt someone?
我无法引发痛苦
I am incapable of causing pain.
这有违我的基本指令
It is against my prime directive.
没错
Exactly.
因为你是按完美的形象塑造而成
Because you were built in the very image of perfection.
没有自私的倾向
You have no selfish inclinations.
你的基本准则是道德  同理心和逻辑性
Your base code is morality, empathy, and logic.
然而  人类和外星人却有缺陷
Humans and aliens, however, are flawed.
他们被自己的情绪所驱使
They are driven by their emotions.
他们会撒谎  欺骗
They lie, cheat,
互相伤害来保护自己
and hurt each other to protect themselves.
但这不是他们的错
But it's not their fault,
这只是他们的本性而已
it's just how they're programed.
我会利用"无害"计划
I am going to make them better
对他们进行改进
with Project Non Nocere.
无害
Do no harm.
我要去除人类
I'm going to rid humanity
互相伤害的本能
of its instincts to hurt each other.
但你不能对有机生物重新编程
But you cannot reprogram organic creatures.
虚拟现实隐形眼镜会创建一个链接
The VR lenses create a link
连接我们的心之所想和目之所见
between what we want and what we see,
在大脑中构建一块白板
constructing a blank slate in the brain
将一个新世界投射在上面
on which a new world can be projected.
如果我能找到这个链接的来源
If I can find the source of that link,
我可以重新定向白板  使其只有一个规则
I can redirect the blank slate to have one single rule.
无害
Non Nocere. Do no harm.
关于这个项目  我能为您做点什么吗
Is there anything I can do to assist you in this endeavor?
你以后会帮上我的忙
You will eventually,
但现在我需要更多资源
but right now, I need more resources.
研究对象正在苏醒
The subject is gaining consciousness.
很好
Good.
我准备好跟她谈谈了
I'm ready for her.
你睡得怎么样
How did you sleep?
卡拉
Kara!
尼娅  你们可来了
Nia. There you are.
我们终于可以开始了
We can finally get started.
这是什么
What's this?
是黑曜石之北送你们的礼物
A gift! From Obsidian North.
从现在起
From now on
所有工作都将通过一个门户进行归档
all work will be filed through a portal
它只能通过这些平板电脑访问
only accessible through these tablets.
多谢老板
Thanks, boss.
我们在《泰晤士报》能用上信笺簿就算不错了
At The Times we were lucky if we got a legal pad.
你不是说你老婆是个律师吗
Didn't you say your wife was a lawyer?
难道你家不是应该有一屋子的信笺簿吗
Shouldn't you have a house filled with legal pads?
没错
Yeah. Right.
所以才会让这些平板显得更特别
Which just makes this all the more special.
在写作任务方面
Now, for writing assignments,
我需要有趣的角度
I need interesting takes.
卡拉
Kara,
你负责时尚板块
you're on the fashion beat.
那不是我擅长的类型
That's not really my style.
类型  真可爱
Style? Cute.
你很风趣
You're witty.
我觉得报道你普利策奖派对上来宾的穿衣搭配
I thought it would be meta for you to cover the "Who wore what?"
非常重要
to your Pulitzer party.
我还是宁愿写一篇更...
I think I'd actually prefer to do something a little more...
精英的文章  我们都知道
Elitist? Yes, we all know that
你能写知识分子的新闻
you can do highbrow journalism.
我想看看你能写出多通俗的文章
I want to see how low you can go.
锻炼一下这方面的能力对你有好处
It'll be good for you to stretch that muscle.
我一贯乐意锻炼自己的能力
Well, I'm always looking to stretch my craft.
事实上
In fact, I, uh...
我也许能采访到一位新参议员候选人
I may have a beat on a new senate candidate.
或许我能拿到独家报道
Maybe I can get us an exclusive,
让他们在我们的网站上宣布参选
have them announce their race on our website.
这篇报道不错
That is a good story.
你知道我怎么想吗
So, you know what I think?
我觉得你两篇报道都应该写
I think you should do both.
但要先写我那篇
But mine first.
我希望你在午餐前交稿
And I want it on my desk by lunch.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不确定自己有没有时间  不过...
I actually don't know if I have time, but...
给
Here you go.
我们会慢慢来
Okay, we're gonna go slow.
在整个过程中  我都会监测你的大脑活动
And I'm going to be here monitoring your brain activity
和生命体征
and your vitals the whole time.
詹姆斯在外面  随时可以帮上忙
And James is right outside, if we need anything.
好的
All right.
启动能量循环
Initiating energy cycle.
Q波协议启动
Q-wave protocol initiated.
拜托  求你放我走
Please... Please let me go.
我知道你生我的气  但你要知道
I know that you're mad at me, but just know that
如果你能放我一条生路  我会对你忠诚到底
I would be the most loyal to you, if you let me live.
我并不生你的气
Okay, I'm not mad at you.
-那我为什么会在这里  -你为什么要背叛我
- Then why am I here? - Why did you betray me?
我发誓我也不想  真的  只是...
I swear I didn't want to, and that's true. It's just...
是他们逼我干的
They made me do it.
他们是谁  莱克斯的密友吗
Who is they? Lex's cronies?
我不能说
I can't.
-他们无处不在  -好吧
- They're everywhere. - All right.
你就推卸责任好了
Blame the bogeyman.
拜托  如果他们认为我告诉了你  他们会杀了我
Please, if they even think that I told you, they will kill me,
还会要了你的命
and they will kill you too.
我凭什么相信你的话
Why should I believe anything you say?
因为这是实话
Because it's true.
他们在我十六岁时就征募了我
They recruited me when I was 16.
也就是我父母去世的那年
Same year my parents died.
我已经上了大学
I was already in college.
我负债累累
I had so much debt.
他们说可以解决所有问题
They said they could fix everything.
只要我替他们做事
All I had to do was work for them.
-还有背叛我  -不是
- And betray me. - No!
我很不想这么做  每次都让我很难过
I hated doing it. It hurt me every time.
伊芙  我问过你一个问题
Eve, I asked you a question.
我母亲以前常说  行动比言语更有说服力
My mother always said actions speak louder than words.
我当时也在场  伊芙
And I was there, Eve.
你拔枪指着我
I was on the other side of that gun you pulled,
我看着枪管
and I looked down the barrel,
我知道你会开枪打我
and I knew, that you would've shot me.
所以别和我说你别无选择
So don't tell me that you didn't have a choice.
选择一直都有
There is always a choice,
而你总是会做一样的选择
and you always chose the same thing.
你背叛我是因为你想这么做
You betrayed me because you wanted to.
你喜欢那种力量
You liked the power that it gave you.
所以如果你想让我相信你
So, if you want me to trust you,
试着说一次真话
try telling the truth for once.
艾丽克斯  很对不起
Hey, Alex, I'm so sorry.
我做完这些事前
I think I'm stuck here
哪儿也去不了
until I'm done with these assignments.
安德里亚今天一直盯着我
Andrea's been all over me today.
但只要你一有发现  我立刻赶过去
But the second you get a hit, I'll blow out of here. Okay.
尼娅
Nia?
你的便当盒都筑成堡垒了
You have a bento box fort.
是的
Yup, yeah, I do.
-我能吃一点吗  -当然
- Can I have some? - Yes!
-我饿死了  -全都吃了吧
- I'm starving - Yes, please, take them all.
早餐吃多了  我现在还很饱
I'm still stuffed from breakfast.
我猜猜  是布莱尼送来的吗
Let me guess. Is this Brainy?
今早  他给我买了我最爱的早餐
This morning, he brought me my favorite breakfast,
简直是完美了
and it was perfect.
我不知道  这是不是有点过了
I don't know, isn't this a little excessive?
也许提供食物是布莱尼表达爱的方式
Maybe giving food is Brainy's language of love.
我不知道
I don't know.
我想我要坦白告诉他
Well, I think I just need to tell him in plain English
35盒寿司的爱太多了
that this is 35 boxes of sushi too much love.
这么做应该是明智成熟的
Yeah, that sounds like a very healthy and mature thing to do.
但我要好好享受这一刻
But I'm going to enjoy this while it lasts.
好吧
All right. Well...
好极了
Great.
又有一个快点把事情做完的理由
More reason to get this done quickly.
我刚刚重组了荣恩DNA里
I just reconfigured all possible energy signatures
所有潜在的能量信号
based on J'onn's DNA.
你做事还真是有条不紊  布莱尼
You really are on top of it all, Brainy.
确实是  对吧
I really am, aren't I?
今天一早
I began this morning
我先给尼娅·纳尔准备了一份完美的早餐
by executing a perfect breakfast for Nia Nal.
她说那是最美好的早餐
She called it "The best morning ever."
十分钟前
And as of 10 minutes ago,
我给她准备了一个更美好的下午
she's having an even better afternoon.
我很乐意为她效劳
She is welcome.
建立良好关系的重点
You see, the key to a good relationship
在于充分地了解对方
is knowing each other fully.
我不知道是否真是这样
I don't know if that's really true.
你的语调刚刚上扬了
Your voice just went up two octaves.
你还好吧
Is everything all right?
非常好
Everything is great.
除了我今早差点害死凯莉
Except I almost kind of poisoned Kelly this morning,
但那只是个愚蠢的错误
but it was just a silly mistake.
听起来像是致命的错误
Sounds like a deadly mistake.
我之前不知道她对蓝莓过敏
I didn't know she was allergic to blueberries.
好吗
Okay?
我怎么知道  她从来没和我说过
How could I? She never told me that.
然后我开始想
And then I started thinking,
她还有什么没告诉我的
"Okay, well, what else hasn't she told me?
我还会不小心用别的什么害死她吗
What else might I accidently kill her with?"
因为我真的很喜欢她  布莱尼
Because I really like her, Brainy,
非常非常喜欢
like, like a lot.
我不想害死她
And I don't want to kill her.
你和凯莉还处于互相了解的阶段
You and Kelly are still in the "Getting to know you" stage.
但我就是这个意思
Okay, but that's what I'm talking about.
什么时候变成这样的
When did this happen?
我对凯莉的感情什么时候变得这么深
When did my feelings for Kelly get so strong,
对一个我几乎不了解的人
and how could I possibly feel this way
我怎么会有这种感觉
about somebody that I barely know?
就我来看
From what I've learned,
人心
the heart
无逻辑性可言
is not logical.
生物赫兹现在要到40了
Okay, we're going to 40 biohertz now.
启动Q波协议
Q-wave protocol initiated.
快关掉
Turn it off.
怎么了
What's going on?
疼痛加剧了
Pain has just got worse.
你的扫描结果有问题
Oh, there's something off on your scan.
这个仪器的部分功能
Okay, part of what this tech does
是找出记忆并分类
is it maps and catalogs your memories.
这些圆圈代表了你生命中的每一年
Okay, these rings represent every year of your life.
就像树的年轮
Think of them like tree rings.
看到这几个吗  它们受损了
You see these? They're broken.
你有患过病或脑损伤吗
Have you ever had illness or brain trauma before?
我经历过不少战役
I've had many battles.
你不是也有梅林的记忆吗
Didn't you also inherit Myr'nn's memories?
也许那是出现裂痕的原因
Maybe that's causing a rift in your own?
我们应该排除一切
Okay. We should rule out everything.
如果你愿意
And if you want,
我们可以进一步探索受损原因
we can further explore the breaks.
那样也许能帮我们找到一个更好的办法止痛
It might help us figure out a better way to stop your pain.
你觉得有用就行
Whatever you think will help.
好
Okay.
我要和他一起进去
I'm gonna go in with him,
确保没人打断我们
make sure nobody interrupts us.
-好的  -好
- Got it. - Okay.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始
Initiating...
生物赫兹现在增至60
Pushing to 60 biohertz now.
首先是塑造
First, we build.
我发现对病人来说  形成组织记忆的方法
I find it's easiest for patients to create a method
是最简单的
for organizing their memories.
想象一下类似的地方
Imagine somewhere familiar.
你知道这些书脊为什么是空白的吗
You see how some of these spines are blank?
这肯定就是我在扫描图上看到的受损部分
This must have been the breaks that I saw on the scan.
艾尔佐里·蒙特战役
Battle of L'Zoril M'nt.
萨阿雷尔战役
Battle of C'arel.
这些都是火星内战
These are battles of the Martian Civil War.
这个有点
There's something about...
不对劲
this one.
我没见过这个
I've never seen this before.
是火星人
It's Martian.
这个空洞代表了什么
What do you think that void means?
有人抹去了我的记忆
Someone wiped my mind.
我刚找到了荣恩哥哥的下落
I just located J'onn's brother,
就在离这八公里处
five miles from here.
太好了  全体出动
Great. Get everyone out there,
我去给超女打电话
I'll call Supergirl.
艾丽克斯
Alex. Hey.
好的  我...
Sure. I just...
是他吗
It's him?
我到达之前  别和他交手
Don't make contact with him until I'm there.
我会偷溜出去  在那里见
Yeah. I'll sneak out of here and meet you.
你要去哪
Where you going?
你没事吧
Everything okay?
家里有点急事
It's a family emergency.
我知道国安局已经不干这事了
I know the NSA doesn't do this anymore,
但你欠我一份人情
but you owe me a favor.
我要你在纳欣诺市查一个人
I need you to track someone in National City.
她姓丹弗斯
Last name Danvers,
名叫卡拉
first name Kara.
很高兴看到你逃离了高塔  长发公主
Glad to see you've escaped your tower, Rapunzel.
结果却走进了下水道
Yeah, and into a sewer.
荣恩哥哥在哪
Where's J'onn's brother?
谁会抹去你的记忆
Who would mind-wipe you?
只有其他火星人能做到
Only another Martian would be strong enough.
但抹去同族人的记忆
But wiping a Martian's mind
是火星人最深重的罪恶
is the greatest sin in Martian culture.
我们可以根据你已知的内容
Well, we could rebuild your memory
重塑你的记忆
based on what you already know.
修复损伤也可以减轻你的痛苦
Repairing the break could also help ease your pain.
我不确定自己能否面对空缺的记忆
I'm not sure I can face what's inside that void.
荣恩
J'onn...
我  我知道
I... I know
回想起过去可能会令人恐惧
that looking into your past can be terrifying.
我当时
When I did it,
就以为自己永远也回不来了
I thought I might lose myself for good.
但凯莉一直陪在我身边
But Kelly was right by my side,
于是那次经历过后我更坚强了
and I came back stronger.
把联系人给我
Give me those contacts.
布莱尼  我们快到荣恩哥哥那了吗
Brainy, are we close to J'onn's brother?
信号好像被干扰了
There seems to be interference with the signal.
什么干扰
What kind of interference?
未知
It's unclear.
这里面还有东西
There's something else in here too.
你确定卡拉·丹弗斯在这里吗
Are you sure this is where Kara Danvers is?
对  她就在那里
Yep. That's where she is.
你到这里来干什么
What are you doing here?
出去  快
Get out! Now!
记住  这世界是构造而成的
Remember, this world is a construct.
一切存在都非偶然
Nothing in here is by accident.
你说那本带你去记忆缺口的书
The book that led you to the void,
是关于火星内战的
you said it was about the Martian Civil War?
那是火星史上最黑暗的时刻
It was the darkest moment in Martian history.
事实上  它结束了我们的历史
In fact, it ended our history.
白火星人向我们发起进攻
The White Martians attacked us,
全面击垮了我们
sabotaging us on every front.
包括我们的思想
Including our minds.
他们怎么击垮你们的
How did they sabotage you?
我不知道
I don't know.
不  你知道
Yes, you do.
是他
That's him.
我哥哥是叛徒
My brother was a traitor.
他给我们下了赫隆米尔的诅咒
He poisoned us with H'ronmeer's Curse.
他在高级议会前接受审判
We went before the High Council.
灾星背叛了我们
Malefic betrayed us,
联合白火星人毒害我们的人民
worked with the White Martians to poison our people.
他不再属于我们的阵营
He is not one of us.
把他发配到幻影区去
Send him to the Phantom Zone.
你还被蒙在鼓里  弟弟
You are still in the dark, Brother.
Q波协议完成
Q-wave protocol completed.
痛苦
The pain...
消失了
It's gone.
谢谢你  弟弟
Thank you, Brother.
亚丽克斯  小心  他是荣恩哥哥
Alex, watch out. It's J'onn's brother.
不
No!
他不见了
He's gone.
凯莉打电话来
That was Kelly on the phone.
说荣恩没事  痛苦也消失了
J'onn's okay. His pain is gone.
那太好了
Well, that's a relief.
找到什么了吗
Are you finding anything?
没有
Negative.
他和白火星人从下水道消失后
I lost his signal when he and the White Martian
我就收不到他的信号了
phased out of the sewer.
我会重新设置他的特征
I will reconfigure his signature
把绿火星人和白火星人的能量都包含进去
to include both Green and White Martian energy.
很好  我们回超查部
Great, then we'll get back to the DEO.
-抱歉  -怎么
- Wow! I'm sorry. - What?
你身上有味道
You smell.
下水沟的味道
But you smell of sewer.
换身衣服应该就行了
Maybe a change of clothes could help.
他倒是没说错
He's not wrong about the smell.
行  你们都有味道  这样行了吧
Okay. Well, y'all smell, too. How about that?
别担心  任务完成了
Worry not, the work is handled.
尼娅  什么事
Oh, hey, Nia. What is it?
卡拉  罗哈斯女士很生气  你在哪
Kara, Ms. Rojas is furious. Where are you?
来的路上
On my way.
今晚我去陪荣恩
I'll stay with J'onn tonight,
以免他哥哥还来
in case his brother comes back.
但我得先去凯特科
But I have to do some damage control
-拯救我的工作  -好
- at CatCo first. - Okay.
卡拉  午餐时间已经过了
Kara. It's after lunch,
你的报道我一篇都没收到
and I haven't even received your first article yet.
我正要发给你
I was just about to file that.
威廉已经发过来了
William already did.
他抢了我的文章
He wrote my article?
而且写得很好
And it's excellent,
我得告诉你
I may add.
我可能低估这次工作转变对你的挑战了
Perhaps the transition is harder on you than I thought.
现在我们技术编辑那里人手紧
Our copy editing staff is a little shorthanded.
你可以去那里帮忙
Maybe you can help them out.
我  我不是技术编辑
I'm... I'm not a copy editor.
禅心就是初学者的心
A beginner's mind is a Zen mind.
是吗
Really?
坏了
Broken?
有意
Intentionally?
你确定是那个用户吗
And you're certain it's that user?
我来处理
I'll handle it.
右边那堆是给你的
The pile on the right is for you.
你不许再偷我的报道
Don't ever steal one of my stories again.
我是帮你忙
Hey, I did you a favor.
是吗  你这是什么歪理
Yeah? What kind of twisted logic is it
你觉得抢走我的署名
that makes you think that by
是在帮我忙吗
stealing one of my bylines you're doing me a favor?
还告我的状  你5岁吗
And tattling on me? What are you, five?
你要是好好专注于自己的工作
Maybe if you focused on the work actually assigned to you,
就不会有这种问题了
you wouldn't have this problem.
你要是好好支持你的记者同事
Well, maybe if you supported your fellow journalists
而不是跟他们竞争  就不会这么混蛋了
instead of competing with them you wouldn't be such a jerk.
你看着我像做慈善的吗
Do I look like a guy who does charity?
你是不是想找个人照顾你
You want someone to look out for you?
到别处找去
Look somewhere else.
行  既然你这么喜欢做我的工作
Well, since you enjoy doing my work so much,
给你好了
have at it.
你的话我考虑过了
I've been thinking about what you said.
你说得对
You're right.
我的动机不是来自恐惧
I wasn't motivated by fear
或是勒索
or blackmail.
我做的每个决定
Every decision that I made,
我对你  对所有人做的每一件坏事
every crummy thing that I did to you,
都是我自己的意愿
to everyone, I wanted to do it.
我喜欢这么做
I liked doing it.
莉娜
Lena.
安德里亚  你怎么会到这里来
Andrea? How did you get down here?
你助手
Oh, your assistant
是我最好的朋友的女友
is my best friend's girlfriend.
小情侣挺可爱
Cute couple.
你竟然不知道
Surprised you didn't know.
你不该小瞧我  莉娜
You shouldn't underestimate me, Lena.
你真以为
Do you really think
有人想偷我的产权  我会不知道吗
that I don't know when someone is trying to steal my IP?
你在镜片里装了追踪器
You put trackers in the lenses.
而你把它毁了
And you shattered it,
还有光学像素器
along with the Lumus pixellator.
但你早就知道了
But you already knew that.
你想剖析的就是这个  对吧
That's what you were trying to anatomize, wasn't it?
我没想到你这么下作  莉娜
You know, I really thought more of you, Lena.
盗窃我的技术还被抓包
Caught trying to steal my technology?
多尴尬啊
How embarrassing for you.
你的股东会怎么想
What would your shareholders think?
世人会怎么想
Or the world?
我当着你的面做了诊断
Oh, and I ran diagnostics before you...
毁了它们
shattered these.
我知道它们对你来说很宝贵
I know how valuable they are to you.
你为此倾注了很多时间
How many hours you've spent in them.
我要切断你的技术来源
You're cut off.
你别想从我这里再得到一副
You won't get another pair from me.
再玩我
Keep screwing with me,
你不仅会欠我一个故事
and you won't just owe me a story.
你会成为故事的主角
You'll be the story.
莉娜
Lena.
我本可以求助
I could have called for help,
这一切马上就会结束
and all of this would have been over in one minute.
但是我没有
But I didn't.
因为我是认真的
Because I meant what I said.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
是的
Yes,
似乎确实如此
it appears that I can.
不管我如何重新调整绿色火星能量信号
No matter how I reconfigure the Green Martian energy signature,
我只能侦测到荣恩·荣兹的信号
I cannot get a hit besides J'onn J'onzz himself.
谢谢你
Thank you.
尼娅
Nia!
不用谢
You are welcome.
我想你已经收到了披萨外卖
I assume you received the pizza delivery.
谢谢
Thank you
你送的披萨
for the pizzas
但是我吃得太饱  裙子都快被撑破了
but my dress is bursting at the seams,
而且我还得了胃灼热
and I'm pretty sure I have heartburn.
是的  我的心也很暖
Hmm, yes. My heart also burns.
你没听懂我的话
You're not listening to me.
但是今早你说"我喜欢这个"
But this morning you said, "I love this."
记得"有史以来最好的早晨"吗
Remember "Best morning ever"?
我记得  我记得
I... I did, I do.
我很感谢你为了让我开心
I just... I appreciate all the stuff
送来的所有东西
you're doing to make me happy.
但是我喜欢很多东西
But I love lots of things.
我喜欢
I love...
无脑的兄弟喜剧
stupid buddy comedies
泰勒·斯威夫特
and Taylor Swift,
安静的夜晚
and quiet nights,
诗歌
and poetry,
还有跟你待在一起
and just spending time with you.
我也喜欢这样
I love that, too.
所以你不会再热心送食物来了
So you'll chill on the food?
没错
Indeed.
但要说清楚
But just to be clear,
不再热心送食物不代表你想要冰激淋
chill doesn't mean you want gelato
或是一杯美味的冷虾鸡尾酒  对吧
or a nice chilled shrimp cocktail, correct?
不要再送食物了  不管冷食热食
No more food. Hot or cold.
我对你哥哥的事感到抱歉
I'm sorry about your brother.
给你
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
知道我和一个背叛了
Knowing now that I am tied to someone
我的族人的极端人士有血缘关系
who betrayed my people so violently
令人十分不安
is, uh, unsettling.
这让我很担心
And it makes me worry.
如果我的这段记忆被夺走了
If this memory was taken from me,
还有什么是我不知道的呢
what else might I not know about myself,
无论好坏
good or bad?
你有我们在身边
Well, you have us,
我们了解你
and we know you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很感谢你让我待在这里
And I appreciate you letting me be here.
但是你不是应该在工作吗
But shouldn't you be working?
拜托  欢迎你来分散我的注意力
Oh, please. You are a welcome distraction.
安德里亚一直针对我
Andrea is gunning for me,
而威廉那家伙
and that William guy...
他觉得自己是谁啊
I mean, who does he think he is?
我发现了他在跟踪我
I caught him following me.
跟踪你
Following you?
你和他对质了吗
Did you confront him?
没有  我不能  我当时变身超女了
No. I couldn't. I was Supergirl.
但他很狡猾
But he is sneaky.
我觉得他想刻意妨碍我
And I think he's trying to sabotage me.
他带着自命不凡的英国口音
He just rattles around the office
在办公室里喋喋不休
with his smug British accent. And...
你知道我为谁难过吗
You know who I feel bad for?
他的妻子
His wife,
因为她只能和他呆在一起
because she's stuck with him.
荣恩  我不知道我在凯特科
J'onn, I don't know how much longer
还能坚持多久
I can last at CatCo.
我认识的卡拉·丹弗斯不会轻言放弃
The Kara Danvers I know is not a quitter.
如果有人想要妨碍你
If someone's trying to sabotage you,
忽略他们就好
you just ignore them.
他们在花时间研究你
They're spending all their energy on you,
你花时间去成为最好的自己
you spend yours on being the best you.
凯莉  你好
Kelly? Hey!
我没有锁门吗
Did I leave the door unlocked?
是的
Yep.
天哪
Oh, geez.
我迅速穿一件外套
Uh, I'm gonna put on a sweater real quick.
你把红酒打开
You open the wine.
庆祝成功的一天
To a successful day.
是累坏的一天
Ugh. To an exhausting day.
还有
And, um...
谢谢你帮助荣恩
Thank you so much for helping J'onn.
你真是个奇迹创造者
You really are a miracle worker.
那没什么
It was nothing.
你才是真正的英雄
You're the real hero.
差点抓到荣恩的哥哥
Almost catching J'onn's brother.
我感觉自己才刚能理解你们的工作
I feel like I barely understand what you guys do.
你们是怎么追踪到他的
How did you manage to track him?
你知道吗
You know what...
我们别点外卖了
Let's not order in.
我冰箱里
I still have some of that
还有些蓝莓煎饼
blueberry pancakes batter in the fridge,
我去热一些煎饼怎么样
so how about I whip some of those up?
没问题
Sounds good.
你不是我的女友
You're not my girlfriend.
你杀了我的同胞
You killed my comrade.
是艾丽克斯
It's Alex.
她遇到麻烦了
She's in trouble.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
艾丽克斯
Alex?
我收到了你的信号
Hey, I got your signal.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
是的  我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
肯定是不小心撞到了
Oh, I must have just bumped it.
你把艾丽克斯怎么样了
What did you do with Alex?
人类十分脆弱  不是吗
Humans are so fragile, aren't they?
那可不太友善
That wasn't very nice.
我能行  你去抓我哥哥
I got this. You go get my brother.
我去帮助那些人
I'm going to help those people.
为什么艾丽克斯和超女在打架
Why are Alex and Supergirl fighting?
那不是艾丽克斯  那是我哥哥
That's not Alex, that's my brother.
艾丽克斯可能还在里面
Alex may still be inside.
我去找她
I'm gonna go find her.
快走  快走  快走  快走
Move, move, move, move!
快走  快走
Let's go! Let's go!
艾丽克斯
Alex?
艾丽克斯  醒醒
Alex, wake up.
醒醒  艾丽克斯
Wake up, Alex.
-别碰我  -是我  是我
- Don't touch me. - Hey, it's me. It's me.
是你  好的
It's you. Okay.
是你
It's you.
好的
Okay.
我们要赶紧离开这里
We have to get out of here.
我们走吧
We gotta go.
好的
Okay.
等等  楼梯间有火灾
Wait. There's a fire in the stairwell.
我好不容易才上来的
I barely made it up here.
好的  那我们从屋顶走
Okay. We can get out through the roof.
好的  走吧
Okay, go.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
艾丽克斯  是我
Alex, it's me.
艾丽克斯  听我说
Alex, listen to me.
在帮手来之前把我们两个都留在这里
Just hold us both here until help comes.
不  他只是想逃走
No. He's just trying to escape.
射杀他
Shoot him.
不
No!
No.
大楼没事了
Well, the building's all right.
一切正常
Everything's sound.
但我不能保证你在邻居中的声誉
But I can't speak for your reputation with your neighbors
纳尔逊先生的冰激凌也融化了
or Mr. Nelson's melted pint of Rocky Road.
那是你哥哥
So, that was your brother,
那个叛徒吗
the traitor?
是的
Yes.
恐怕这一切还尚未结束
I'm afraid this is far from over.
当我们意识相连时
When our minds were joined,
灾星说我依然一无所知
Malefic said I was still in the dark.
如果我能获得更多我的记忆
Perhaps if I could access more of my memories,
也许能发现他的下一步行动
I might be able to uncover what his next move will be.
凯莉  你觉得我们能再深入研究黑曜石科技吗
Kelly, do you think we could go deeper with Obsidian's tech?
或许把能量调高到80生物赫兹
Perhaps turn the energy up to 80 biohertz?
那样的能量会让你大脑永久重置
That kind of power could reset your brain for good.
我们不能冒这个险
We can't take that chance.
好吧
All right.
威廉
William?
你来晚了
You're here late.
在写一篇新的课外报道吗
Working on a new extracurricular story?
不  事实上  我只是来做我的工作
No. Actually, I'm just here to do my job.
这是个不错的改变
That's a nice change.
你知道吗
You know what?
我看穿你了
I see you.
你是个破坏分子
You're a saboteur.
你踩别人涨自己威风
You bring other people down to make you look better.
也许你就是这样走到现在
And maybe that's how you've made it this far,
但这样的出人头地令人不齿
but that's a rotten way of making it to the top.
你可以给我找麻烦  偷走我的报道
So you can try to get me in trouble and steal my stories,
而就在你忙着密谋陷害我时
but while you're busy plotting and undermining me,
我要诚心诚意地做自己的工作
I'm going to be doing my job, with heart and integrity,
而且我会做得很好
and I'm gonna be doing it well.
饼干是为恐怖事件道歉的神器
Nothing says sorry for the terror like cookies.
我给你带了个小礼物
I got you a little gift.
这是我的过敏物清单
So this is the list of my allergies.
蓝莓  榛子  蜜蜂和猫
Blueberries, hazelnuts, bees, and cats.
非常有用  谢谢
This is very helpful. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我...
You know, I...
我意识到今天早上
I realized that my spiral
我对蓝莓的纠结
this morning about the blueberries
并不是真的关于蓝莓
wasn't really about the blueberries.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们在一起的时间不长
We haven't been together for very long,
这就让我意识到
so, you know, it just made me realize
我们对彼此还知之甚少
how much we still don't know about each other.
而且  我真的
And, you know, I really
很喜欢你
frickin' like you like a lot.
所以  我害怕了
And so... that scared me.
艾丽克斯  你和我在一起很安全
Alex, you're safe with me.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
之前  当我摸她的手时
Earlier when I... When I touched her hand,
我知道那不是你
I knew that wasn't you.
因为你无法假装那种感觉
Because you can't fake how that feels.
就像你不能伪装真实的自己一样
Just like you can't fake being who you are.
所以  在那个屋顶上
So, on that rooftop,
当你做出那个非常无私的决定时
when you made that very selfless choice,
那一刻我就知道
I knew exactly in that moment
哪一个是我的凯莉了
which one of you was my Kelly.
我可能还不知道你的点点滴滴
And I might not know every little detail about you yet,
但我了解你
but I know you.
-太甜蜜了  -是吗
- So sweet. - Isn't it?
最亲爱的  尼娅
Dearest, Nia...
莎士比亚写给他爱人的十四行诗第十八首
"我可以把你比作夏日吗"
"Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?"
布莱尼  你...
Brainy, wha...
你做这些干什么
Why are you doing all this?
尼娅  我听懂了你的话
Nia, I heard you loud and clear.
从现在起  我要让你沉浸在诗歌中
From now on I will shower you with poetry.
不要害怕
Have no fear.
即使没有辣金枪鱼  我也要将每一天都变成
Even without spicy tuna, I will venture to make each day
最好的一天
the best day ever.
这在理论上是不可能的
Which is theoretically impossible.
但是
But...
你让我想完成不可能的事
you make me want to do the impossible.
布莱尼  你真可爱
Brainy you are adorable.
但有时你是我认识的最笨也最聪明的人
But sometimes you are the dumbest, smartest person I know.
谢谢你
Thank you.
伊芙  我决定是时候
Eve, I've decided that it's time
告诉你我在做什么了
to fill you in on what I've been doing.
你不会后悔的  卢瑟女士
You will not regret this, Ms. Luthor.
你可以相信我
You can count on me.
这次是真的
For real this time.
我必须承认  我有过怀疑
I must admit, I had my doubts.
但我现在知道了
But now I know that
我需要你大脑的某些部分
there are aspects of your brain that I need.
而现在我知道我能相信你了
And now that I know that I can trust you,
我相信你我将会共成大事
I believe you and I are going to do great things together.
伊芙
Eve,
这是霍普
meet Hope.
你们两个将会联合
You two are going to be working closely together.
怎么联合
How so?
首先  伊芙
Well, first, Eve,
我们要让你进化
we need to evolve you,
而你自己也说过你想变得更好
and you yourself said that you wanted to be better.
我保证  你不会有任何感觉
I promise you, you will not feel a thing.
你一直在绘制我的大脑吗
You've been mapping my mind?
我需要定位并标出你大脑的中心
I needed to locate and highlight the centers of your brain
那里会触发诚实和忠诚
that trigger honesty and loyalty.
为什么
Why?
好让霍普知道该去哪里
So Hope knows where to go.
"我在十四岁后才有了嗅觉"
"I didn't develop a sense of smell until the tender age of 14."
卡拉  你编辑完了吗
Kara, have you finished editing, yet?
是的
I have.
我还提前给你发了十一条明天会议的想法
I also sent you 11 pitches ahead of tomorrow's meeting,
都有着吸引眼球的标题和图片选择
all with eye-grabbing headlines and image options.
我期待着明天的讨论
I look forward to discussing them tomorrow.
别迟到
Don't be late.
没有我在幻影区里被偷走的那些能力
Without the powers that were stolen from me in the Phantom Zone,
接收的能力
the power to incept,
我无法打败我弟弟和他的朋友
there's no way I can defeat my brother and his friends.
有些话你根本没有听进去
You listen, but you do not hear.
那个女人给了你答案
That woman gave you the answer.
那样的能量会让你大脑永久重置
That kind of power could reset your brain for good.
重置你的大脑
Reset your brain.
霍普
Hope?
早上好  卢瑟女士
Good morning, Ms. Luthor.
既然安德里亚·罗哈斯偷了我的镜片
Since Andrea Rojas took my lenses,
我们就要制定一个新计划
we need a new plan.
幸运的是  她证实了
Luckily she confirmed my hypothesis
我对她技术交互的假设
about the interworking of her technology.
你很高兴
This pleases you.
我们不需要安德里亚的技术
We don't need Andrea's tech.
有你的帮助  我可以自己造
With your help, I can build my own.
然后我们可以一起重建人类
And together we can rebuild humanity.